oh women are different and weird
i'm gonna do that too first thing i
don't understand
[Music]
when i got married i learned something
very quick
i'm never gonna ask my wife where she
wants to go for dinner
whenever i do ruins the night we just
get in a fight
so men i started doing this when i get
home
i find my wife i go up to her
and i excitedly say hey
guess where i'm taking you for dinner
tonight
and whatever she says that's where we go
that's a life hack life hacks are things
that make your life easier
but because it's your wife it's a wife
hack
now i love my wife she is the most
amazing person
in my world and i i wouldn't be as a
good a person now
if it weren't for her there's a lot of
comedians that will poke fun and they'll
make fun of their significant others and
wives
and they'll be like oh women are
different and weird
i'm gonna do that too first thing i
don't understand
[Music]
first thing holiday candles you know
what i'm talking about the christmas
scented candles
the ones that are scented like evergreen
balsam holly jolly gumdrop nonsense
first thing my wife does after christmas
ends she boxes them all
up she runs and she puts them in a
closet in the basement where we can't
find them next year because that's a fun
game
first thing she does after boxing up all
the christmas scented candles
goes out and buys all new scented
candles why can't we use christmas
candles all year round
are we worried we're gonna have guests
come over in july they're gonna walk in
and smell them and be like
oh what day is it is that christmas
i've done zero shopping
second thing i don't get catchy little
wooden home signs
you know the wooden signs that have
paragraphs of sayings etched into them
you know the thing you want to read as
soon as you enter someone's house
they have sayings like home is where the
heart is
and a house is just a house
until it's filled with people that you
love
then it's a home
who are these signs for they're not for
me
if they were they would be honest and
they would say
things like home is where my
farts are
and a house is just a house
until i get there immediately take off
my pants
and then it's a home
one thing my wife and i we love to do is
we will watch horror movies together we
love watching horror movies
she'll sit their eyes glued to the tv
wide open
just throwing back gobs of popcorn all
up until the point
in a horror movie when a small animal
like a dog appears as soon as a dog
appears in a horror movie
my wife will snap up and she will go
no
[Laughter]
if they touch one hair
on that poor defenseless animal's head
i'm gonna stop watching this horror
movie
well luckily honey the hockey mask
killer
only kills adults
teenagers super small children
but has a soft spot for shih tzus
and that's why you watch horror movies
you want to see the mutilations
the decapitations but i guess it would
be weird if
before watching a horror movie you were
with someone
and behind you you heard them say
i just want to see how many dogs they
kill
[Laughter]
it's gonna get rough
rough
while watching these horror movies we
realized something especially if you
watch
90s horror movies where you're supposed
to guess who the killer
is like they'll introduce a batch of
teens at the beginning
and it's like oh which one of these is
the killer
never at the end of one of these is the
killer revealed to be the friend
who has the shape and body image
of someone like me
think about it at the end of the movie
the killer's never taken off their mask
and they're like
and the killer was me the whole time
and the teenagers are like y'all we knew
it was you bro
you really uh stretch and fill out that
black robe you're wearing uh
you have like 80 pounds on all of us
also earlier when you were chasing us
through the woods with that axe
you were breathing pretty heavy
at one point we saw you lean up against
a tree are you okay bro
now you all now know who i am
but i don't know who any of you are
so on the count of three i would like
everybody
to say their name okay
great one two three
[Applause]
it's nice to meet you by a round of
applause
how many people have clapped their hands
before
[Music]
no okay those two are dead jokes and i
get to legally tell them now
cause just last week my wife and i
welcomed our daughter our first child
into our home
[Applause]
she was born four months ago but just
last week we welcomed her inside
we said get on in here stranger because
that's what babies are babies are
strangers
that spend all of your money and poop
all day every day
but it was good when i finally had a
child because my friends always said
ricky you have a dad bod
luckily now that i have a kid i think i
have a father figure
also whenever anybody sees our baby
people always
immediately just want to come up to my
wife and i
look at our daughter and say oh
she's the spitting image of her dad
and to be fair i do drool a lot
and it's cute it's okay for them to say
that she looks like me
our baby daughter looks like her dad now
but oh help her if when she's 16
if she looks like this with
a wig ain't nobody asking her to prom
i was born and raised in kentucky went
to high school in kentucky went to
campbell county high school
where our mascot was the camel
we were the campbell county camels
in kentucky our colors
purple and gold you know like a camel
i'm all for alliteration i just wish
that our mascot
could have been something like a tad bit
more intense
like the uh campbell county canines
or the campbell county cobras or the
campbell county cougars
and i'm not talking wildcat i'm talking
like older woman that preys on young men
aggressively that's intense
it got so bad at our football games this
is how
our announcer used to bring us out to
the field
ladies and gentlemen give it up for your
campbell county camels
watch out they spit
i have two older brothers oldest brother
john second oldest brother
eric eric is gay out of the closet
lives in kentucky don't worry he's safe
he came out while he was going to
college in florida
and we were visiting him we were trying
to think of the most
kentucky thing we could do as a family
so he took him to a flea market
and while we were there he took my mom
aside and he said
mom i have something to tell you
i'm gay to which my mom
took a deep breath and replied
whatever you do do not tell your dad and
brother
this will ruin their vacation
so flash forward now i'm going to
college i'm going to college become a
secondary education
english major which is a real long way
to say
underpaid high school teacher two years
in i decide i want to change my major
i want to do theater i want to do
something like this
so i asked my out of the closet brother
eric
to help me tell my parents
so at our regular sunday dinner with the
family
we finished up my brother stood up and
he said
mom and dad ricky has something he wants
to tell you
to which my dad hung his head and said
you're not gay too are you
and my brother said nope but close
i'm pretty sure that before i got
married this is how my mom would talk
about me to strangers
she would have a family photo on her
persons on the ready
and she'd pull it out and she'd be like
this is our son john
he gave us our first grandchild
this is our son eric he's a doctor
and this this is our son ricky
[Laughter]
he has health insurance
but when i got married the uh the first
thing i learned is that
you get way too many photos back of the
reception
if you've gotten married you know this
the only thing wedding photos are good
for
is if you've ever argued with someone
that you're a good
dancer wedding photos will prove you
wrong
[Music]
the other thing i learned is we got like
a thousand photos back of just the
reception
and i hate to sound like an old man but
they all came back on a stick
that you plug into your computer like a
thousand photos
i realize we're never gonna have
physical photos again
like my dad has the last known living
photo
of my great great grandfather from world
war one
in his army fatigues never gonna have
that again
my great great grandchildren they're
gonna be like
on this hologram wristwatch
here are about a thousand photos of your
great-great-grandmother
doing a thing called duckface
and here's about 400 more of her with
long dog ears and a long tongue
apparently we used to be able to change
into animals i don't know what happened
i'm not much of a drinker um i don't
know a lot of drinking terminology
like ipa not sure what it stands for it
could stand for i'm perfectly average
based on the people i've seen drink it
so i met my wife on a dating website and
it worked for us
i i saw her profile if you've ever done
online dating you go there
and you see a bunch of text information
but the first thing you look at is the
picture
you only get one picture and i saw my
wife's picture
and she looked beautiful and the first
thing that drew me in were her eyes
like just by seeing her picture in her
eyes i felt she had a personality
that i just had to meet her had to ask
her on a date
i know right but no i
was like you have to take a chance maybe
it won't work out you ask her out and
then
just roll the dice and then i clicked on
that picture to see the rest of her
pictures
and she only had one more picture
and in that one she was wearing a hat
and i have a theory about women who wear
hats
the bigger the hat the crazier the woman
and this was a fedora so like mid-level
crazy
now i thought that this would be a cute
story
to tell my wife on our one year
anniversary
it was not she got mad
she got mad and she snapped oh oh
i'm wearing a hat now do i look crazy
do i look crazy
and i said yes
it's midnight we're in bed take off the
sombrero
i don't have a great singing voice
but i like to think about like big time
rock stars
they had to have real nine to five jobs
before they made it big
so think how weird would it have been
that if like
brian johnson the lead singer of ac dc
was your server at a restaurant before
he became the lead singer of ac dc
you'd be sitting there and he'd come up
to the table and he'd be like
welcome to the restaurant
we got hot soup and bread rolls yeah
or you're at a grocery store and dave
matthews was bagging your groceries
would you like paper all plastic
i put the bread on top of the eggs
take these groceries
or if like what if some of our favorite
actors became singers
like what if sean connery in the 80s is
like i'm an 80s singer now
and he released the single you can dance
if you want to
or you can leave your friends behind
because if your friends won't dance and
if they don't dance
well i ain't no friends of mine
now people after shows have sometimes
asked me ricky
how do you come up with what celebrities
you can do and can't do
and i tell them i used to do the voices
for my wife
all up until one day when she said
and i quote stop
[Music]
it's 6 a.m it's too early for pee wee
herman
but if you remember to the beginning of
the show
i have a baby now
and babies cannot talk so now i make her
listen
so now every night i dramatically read
to her a nursery rhyme
read by one of my favorite celebrities
like
sylvester stallone they're like yo
yo yo yo boy like gently down the stream
[Laughter]
merrily merrily merrily merrily you know
like life is but a dream you know
or sir alan rickman from harry potter
professor snape
i'm a little teapotter
short and stout here is my handler
here
hey i'm mcdonald he had some animals
i guess that's not weird it's a farm you
should have some animals
michael caine there was a boy
who had a dog and bingo was his name-o
arnold schwarzenegger
around
rogen um
twinkle twinkle little star
uh how i wonder what you are up above
the sky so high
hi
[Laughter]
john c reilly from wreck-it ralph
little miss muffet sat on a tuffet
eating her curds away
then like along came a spider that sat
down beside her
and miss muffet's like you know i think
i'm gonna get out of here
in final nursery rhyme this is one that
my baby definitely doesn't understand
uh this is all of the us presidents in
my lifetime
from 1985 to now dramatically reading
one potato two potato
three potato four
five potato
six potato seven potato more
uh hey potato uh
not potato team potato uh okay we got
all the potatoes
we got the best potatoes we're gonna
grow them locally
we got no collusion with these potatoes
they're going to be huge they're going
to be tremendous
you guys have been awesome tonight you
guys are so
so so cool for coming out here um i got
one impression i gotta leave you with
and this is an impression that everybody
can do if you want to spend five years
working on it
this is my impression of a penguin
looking for his wallet
[Laughter]
so
[Applause]
wow
you